

Rabee AL jaramani – WEB DEVELOPER

Mobile: (+971) 567657124

Date of birth: 17/04/1988

Email Address: rabeealjaramani@yahoo.com

My E-commerce website: https://e-star-x.herokuapp.com/

in Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/rabeih-aljaramani-4b005b193/

Address: Dubai (United Arab Emirates)

Nationality: Syrian

Languages: Arabic, English

ABOUT ME

First-rate Informatics Engineer with +9 years of experience offering outstanding support to users and companies of various levels in different countries. Passionate about web development and seeking to grow in the role of a web developer by using my React, HTML and CSS skills to deliver coding excellence. Ambitious problem solver with a passion for online businesses and would like to join a team of likeminded developers. Constantly striving to improve myself and enhance my skills in technologies.

SKILL SET

- Web Programming & Design: JavaScript, HTML5, Bootstrap, CSS, jQuery, XML, React js, Redux, C#, C++, ASP.net mvc.
- Database Tools: MongoDB and Microsoft SQL.
- High knowledge in programming languages and networking.
- Self-learning.
- Operating systems: Windows (XP, 7, 8, 10), Microsoft Windows Server (2003, 2008, 2016), Mac OS, Android, iOS, Office Tools: Microsoft Office (2003, 2007, 2013, 2016, 2019) Access, Power Point, Word, Excel.
- Computer devices, tablets, mobile phones, servers and networks.
- Security cameras CCTV and IP cameras.
- Teaching programming courses, information technology topics and computer usage.
- Build meeting and class rooms for schools and universities (projectors, mirroring, smart boards
- Data management.
- Quality assurance for applications and devices.
- Projects Management and IT planning to achieve the needs.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Information Technology Support Engineer

Diamond Island for Office Equipment [02/01/2020 – Current]

City: Dubai

Country: United Arab Emirates

- Developing a new system to enhance the work flow between employees and customers.
- Web developer.
- Testing Accounting system and report bugs.
- Hardware and software maintenance.
- Troubleshooting and problem solving.

Information Technology Engineer

Star Computer Company[15/09/2013 - 10/11/2019]

City: Beirut

Country: Lebanon

- Build a database for the company's goods and our customers' details.
- Tracking all tasks and orders.
- Developing Desktop applications on demands.
- Software and hardware maintenance for laptops, desktop computers, tablets, tablet pc's and iPad services.
- Install and maintain networks, terminals and internet access points.
- · Data backup.
- Recover lost or deleted data.
- Security cameras (CCTV and IP cameras) with online access.
- Testing new devices and solve any problems if existed.
- · Customer service.
- Contact with our suppliers in china to make enhancements on the devices.

Teacher

Toyour Aljanna School[01/08/2011 – 01/11/2011]

City: Damascus Country: Syria

> Teaching kids the computer usage and learn them to use the computer as a useful machine for learning goals.

Teacher

Com2Net Institute[01/08/2011 – 01/11/2011]

City: Damascus
Country: Syria

- Teaching ICDL course.
- Teaching ASP.net and C# programming for designing websites.

Computer technician

IT for computers [01/08/2008 – 01/11/2010]

City: Damascus
Country: Syria

- · Installation operating system and programs.
- Assemble Desktop computers.
- Fixing any software or hardware problems.
- · Customer service.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Bachelor degree of Informatics Engineering.

Arab International University (AIU) [15/09/2006 – 15/08/2011]

Address: Daraa Ghabaghib, Damascus (Syria)

https://www.aiu.edu.sy/